

Uju Louisa Adimora

System/Network Administrator
Junior Full Stack Software Developer

Profile

I have gained 9+ years of extensive experience in configuring, managing, and supporting computer network infrastructure, enterprise backup, and Helpdesk, using excellent leadership skills and multitasking strengths. My attention to detail and inquisitive nature have lent itself to immersing myself in a Diploma in Full Stack Software Development. I am eager to enter a noble company where I can grow and contribute positively!



25.11.1976



+49 152140 39314



14 Grönland Str., Bremen



adimorauju@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/adimora-uju-louisa-48b821179



https://ujuadimora-dev.github.io

/my_Potfolia/

Work Experience

July 2018 - date

Career break/Relocation to Germany from Nigeria

- Focus my time learning the German Language and completing a Diploma in Full stack Software development.
- ♣ Part-time Volunteer Worker at Saint Nicolaus Center for Children and Youth Bremen.
- In my free Time, Video Editing / Learning of AWS / Azure / Google Cloud Computing.

2009-July 2018

Team Lead

IT infrastructure Network

ITGENT Limited, Lagos Nigeria

- → Part of a Team that performs Microsoft licensing management and auditing for a bank, saving them millions of dollars.
- ♣ Conducting routine evaluations of network and data security, Locating and seizing chances to enhance and update software and systems, Creating and implementing the organization's IT policy, and using best practices.
- Performing routine system audits, Organizing and establishing deadlines for major IT projects such as system updates, migrations, and upgrades.

2003-October 2003

System/ Network Administrator

Tranter Limited, Lagos Nigeria

- Setting up new networks. Maintaining and upgrading existing computer networks, including hardware like VPNs and routers.
- Troubleshooting flaws in software, hardware configuration, communications equipment, and then fixing problems as they arise.
- Updating and configuring virus protection software and other programs to keep networks secure, monitoring and maximizing network performance.
- Installing and configuring computer systems and network equipment, including local area networks (LANs), wide area networks (WANs), and data communication systems and Communicating updates and problems to other employees, as well as those in management roles.

Education

October 2022-October 2023

Diploma in Full Stack Software Development

Code Institute - Dublin, Ireland - (Credit Rated by University of West of Scotland)

October 2018- November 2021 Deutsch Language

Certificate (Language level B1, B2 and Citizenship)

VHS Bremen Germany.

December 1996- December 2000

Bachelor's in computer science & engineering (B.Eng.)

Enugu State University of Science and Technology, Nigeria.

Technical Skillset

Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Python, Streamlit.

Databases: MySQL, Postgres.

Frameworks: Django, jQuery, Bootstrap.

Version Control: Git, GitHub, VScode, Codeanywhere.

Hosting|plaform|cloud: Google, AWS, Azure, Claudinary, Heroku, Microsoft, Linus.

Machine Learning: NumPy, Pandas, Pytorch, Matplotlib, TensorFlow, Scikit-learn, Jupyter Notebook.

Customer service oriented/Resistance to stress/innovative/good behavior.

Certifications

- Microsoft Certified Professional
- Microsoft Certified System Administrator
- Microsoft Certified System Engineer
- Job Roles un the Cloud(AWS)
- AWS Shares Responsibility(AWS)
- AWS Well-Architect

Interesse/Additional Information

- Participation in the Code Institute Hackathon.
- Fluent Igbo, Fluent English, intermediate
 German
- Machine learning / Video Editing / Learning AWS / Azure / Google Cloud Computing.
- Currently working and updating Afrik-Kichen app(https://afrik-kitchen.herokuapp.com/)

My Most Current Projects

- Ever-young- The site is for those who want to remain Young both body and spirit, It is all about what you need to do or eat to be ever Young. Am sure everyone wants to live healthy and good-looking. It was built with HTML and CSS. Technologies Used HTML5, CSS. GitHub https://ujuadimora-dev.github.io/ever-young
- FunTime-Quiz- This is all about having fun while Playing the Game quiz. Technologies Used HTML5, CSS, and JavaScript. GitHub https://ujuadimora-dev.github.io/FunTime-Ouiz
- Simple Payroll System- This is about accounting system, This project can help organizations update employees' records as well as calculate the net payment for the employees

 Technologies Used -Python GitHub –

 https://simple-payroll-system.herokuapp.com
- Afrik-Kichen- The app is a restaurant management system designed to allow staff to easily manage the food menus, table management, and Table bookings.

 Technologies Used HTML5, CSS with Bootstrap, JavaScript, Python, Django framework, Postgres DB, and Claudinary for hosting media. GitHub https://afrik-kitchen.herokuapp.com/
- Mildew-detection-in-cherry-leaves A Machine learning(AI) site for Detecting and predicting Cherry Leaves that are healthy and infected leaves with powdery Mildew. Technologies Used-Python, Streamlit app, Jupyter Notebook, NumPy, Pandas, Pytorch, Matplotlib, TensorFlow, Scikitlearn. GitHub Yet to be deployed

References are available on request.